Guide to the Donald Kennedy, President of Stanford University, Papers SC0315
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Donald Kennedy, president of Stanford University, papers
1972-2006
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Kennedy, Donald
Stanford University. Office of the President
SC0315
340.25 Linear Feet
Information about Access
Some series are restricted until 2019. Please consult the University Archivist for assistance.
Universities and colleges -- Administration.; Kennedy, Donald; Lyman, Richard W.; Stanford University. Office of the President; Stanford University -- General subdivision--Presidents.
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1983-177
  - Administrative Council, 7/1981-8/1981; AD 4.12 (Box 1, Folder AD 4.12)
  - Administrative Council, 1/1981-6/1981; AD 4.12 (Box 1, Folder AD 4.12)
  - Stanford Overseas Studies, 1/1979-8/1981; AD 8.11 (Box 1, Folder AD 8.11)
  - Housing: Faculty, Staff, Emeriti, 10/1979-7/1981; AD 8.18 (Box 1, Folder AD 8.18)
  - Staff Affirmative Action Program, 5/1979-8/1981; AD 9.6 (Box 1, Folder AD 9.6)
  - Management Self Study, 6/80-8/1981; AD 10.3 (Box 1, Folder AD 10.3)
  - Grievances-Benmayor, 2/1981-8/1982; AD 10.8.0/1 (Box 1, Folder AD 10.8.0/1)
  - Grievances-Chinn, 9/1979-10/1983; AD 10.8.16/1 (Box 1, Folder AD 10.8.16/1)
  - Grievances-Charles Wieder, 4/80-4/1981; AD 10.8.10/1 (Box 1, Folder AD 10.8.10/1)
  - Retirement, 8/76-8/1981; AD 10.8.17 (Box 1, Folder AD 10.8.17)
  - Business and Finance, 1979-8/1981; AD 12.2 (Box 1, Folder AD 12.2)
  - Gift Policies/Gift Summaries, 9/78-8/1980; AD 12.10.3/5 (Box 1, Folder AD 12.10.3/5)
  - Prospective Donors, 1975-6/1983; AD 12.10.3/12 (Box 1, Folder AD 12.10.3/12)
  - Foundations, Misc., 9/78-8/1981; AD 12.10.4 (Box 1, Folder AD 12.10.4)
  - Facilities Planning, 2/1981-8/1981; AD 12.14.7/29 (Box 1, Folder AD 12.14.7/29)
  - Faculty Club, 11/72-5/78; AD 12.14.7/30 (Box 1, Folder AD 12.14.7/30)
  - Office of Undergraduate Studies, 11/78-5/1982; AA 1.12 (Box 2, Folder AA 1.12)
  - Emeriti, 10/80-3/1981; AA 2.2 (Box 2, Folder AA 2.2)
  - Faculty and Academic Appointment Procedures and Policies, 1/1979-8/1981; AA 2.3.2 (Box 2, Folder AA 2.3.2)
  - Human Biology, 5/80-8/1981; AA 4.1.26 (Box 2, Folder AA 4.1.26)
  - Dept. of Athletics, Physical Education and Recreation, 1/1979-8/1981; AA 4.1.30 (Box 2, Folder AA 4.1.30)
  - Graduate School of Business, 1/1979-8/1981; AA 4.2 (Box 2, Folder AA 4.2)
  - School of Earth Sciences, 1976-78; AA 4.3 (Box 2, Folder AA 4.3)
  - School of Engineering, 5/1981-8/1981; AA 4.4 (Box 2, Folder AA 4.4)
  - Mechanical Engineering, 10/80-6/1981; AA 4.4.9 (Box 2, Folder AA 4.4.9)
  - Center for Integrated Systems, 7/80-8/1981; AA 4.4.19 (Box 2, Folder AA 4.4.19)
  - School of Education, 2/1979-8/1981; AA 4.5 (Box 2, Folder AA 4.5)
  - School of Medicine, 1980-8/1981; AA 4.6 (Box 2, Folder AA 4.6)
  - Libraries, 1981; AA 4.12 (Box 2, Folder AA 4.12)
  - RLG/RLIN, 7/80-8/1981; AA 4.12.1 (Box 2, Folder AA 4.12.1)
  - School of Law, 1979-7/1981; AA 4.15 (Box 2, Folder AA 4.15)
  - Stanford University Hospital, 1981; AA 4.17 (Box 3, Folder AA 4.17)
  - Stanford University Hospital, 1/80-1.2/1980; AA 4.17 (Box 3, Folder AA 4.17)
  - CIT (SCIP-SHAW), 12/78-12/1980; AA 4.22 (Box 3, Folder AA 4.22)
  - Endowed Chairs, Professorships, 9/78-12/1982; AA 10 (Box 3, Folder AA 10)
  - SCIP, 1/1981-8/1981; AA 4.22 (Box 3, Folder AA 4.22)
  - McCloskey, 1/1983-9/1983; AA 10 (Box 3, Folder AA 10)
  - California State Government, 4/80-8/1981; G 1.2 (Box 3, Folder G 1.2)
  - Federal Legislature, 9/1979-8/1981; G 3.1 (Box 3, Folder G 3.1)
  - Small Business Set Aside Bill, 1/80-10/1982; G 3.1/1 (Box 3, Folder G 3.1/1)
  - Selective Services/Draft, 5/1979-9/1980; G 3.1.7 (Box 3, Folder G 3.1.7)
  - International Traffic in Arms Regulations, 1981; G 3.7.6 (Box 3, Folder G 3.7.6)
  - Students, Misc., 1979-80; St 1 (Box 4, Folder St 1)
  - Stanford Band, 9/1979-8/1981; St 3.4 (Box 4, Folder St 3.4)
  - Board of Trustees (Misc.), 1981; B 1 (Box 4, Folder B 1)
  - Board of Trustees (Misc.), 1980; B 1 (Box 4, Folder B 1)
  - Boys Town Center, 9/78-8/1981; 1.1 (Box 4, Folder 1.1)
  - H.E.I. Correspondence, 1981; 2.1 (Box 4, Folder 2.1)
  - H.E.I. Correspondence, 1979-80; 2.1 (Box 4, Folder 2.1)
  - H.E.I.-Recruiting-Letters of Recommendation, 2/1981-2/1982; 2.1 (Box 4, Folder 2.1)
  - H.E.I. Reports by Richard Bates, 29707; 2.1 (Box 4, Folder 2.1)
  - H.E.I. EPA Position and Funding, 7/80-4/1981; 2.1 (Box 4, Folder 2.1)
  - H.E.I. Washington Trip, 29587; 2.1 (Box 4, Folder 2.1)
  - H.E.I. Congressional Hearings and Cong. View of EPA, 29677; 2.1 (Box 4, Folder 2.1)
  - H.E.I. Minutes of Meetings, 12/80-7/1981; 2.1 (Box 4, Folder 2.1)
  - H.E.I. Legal Status (IRS) and Developments, 4/1981- 5/1981; 2.1 (Box 4, Folder 2.1)
  - H.E.I. Recruiting and Letters of Recommendation, 3/1981-4/1981; 2.1 (Box 4, Folder 2.1)
  - H.E.I. Letters of Recommendation, 11/1979-5/1981; 2.1 (Box 4, Folder 2.1)
  - H.E.I. Recruiting-Form Letter from DK and Mailing Lists, 2/80-3/1981; 2.1 (Box 4, Folder 2.1)
  - News Clippings and Notes, 1981; 2.1 (Box 4, Folder 2.1)
  - H.E.I. Letters to Auto Manufacturers, 4/80-4/1981; 2.1 (Box 4, Folder 2.1)
  - H.E.I. Chuck Powers-Resume, 2.1 (Box 4, Folder 2.1)
  - H.E.I. Organization of, and By-laws, 8/1979-1/1981; 2.1 (Box 4, Folder 2.1)
  - Senate of the Academic Council, 6/80-5/1981; C 2 (Box 5, Folder C 2)
  - Academic Senate-13th and 14th, 5/80-5/1981; C 2.1 (Box 5, Folder C 2.1)
  - Academic Council, thru 12/1980; C 2 (Box 5, Folder C 2)
  - Advisory Board, 5/80-8/1981; C 3 (Box 5, Folder C 3)
  - Advisory Board Red Folder Meetings, 1/1979- 4/1981; C 3.3 (Box 5, Folder C 3.3)
  - Steering Committee (StC), 9/1979-6/1981; C 4.1 (Box 5, Folder C 4.1)
  - Committee on Committees (CoC), 11/80-5/1981; C 4.2 (Box 5, Folder C 4.2)
  - Gores and Dinkelspiel Citations, 1981; C 5.1.3 (Box 5, Folder C 5.1.3)
  - Gores and Dinkelspiel Awards, 1/1979-6/1980; C 5.1.3 (Box 5, Folder C 5.1.3)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Studies, 1/1981-6/1981; C 5.7 (Box 5, Folder C 5.7)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Studies, 1978-80; C 5.7 (Box 5, Folder C 5.7)
  - Cabinet on Undergraduate Education, 8/80-9/1982; C 5.7/1 (Box 5, Folder C 5.7/1)
  - Univ. Committee on Land Building and Dev., 1980; C 6.6 (Box 5, Folder C 6.6)
  - Inaugurations-Other Schools, 10/80-8/1981; 8.55 (Box 6, Folder 8.55)
  - Inauguration-Donald Kennedy Task Force, 1980; 08.55.1 (Box 6, Folder 08.55.1)
  - Inauguration-Donald Kennedy Responses, 1980; 08.55.1 (Box 6, Folder 08.55.1)
  - Donald Kennedy Inauguration Congratulations Letters, 1980; 08.55.1 (Box 6, Folder 08.55.1)
  - Inauguration-Donald Kennedy Speech, Ceremony, 1980; 08.55.1 (Box 6, Folder 08.55.1)
  - Research, Misc., 1/1979-7/1981; R 0 (Box 6, Folder R 0)
  - Sponsored Projects, 8/1979-8/1981; R 1 (Box 6, Folder R 1)
  - Committee on Research, 12/80-6/1981; R1.2 (Box 6, Folder R1.2)
  - Stanford Center for Chicano Research, 8/80-7/1981; R1.3 (Box 6, Folder R1.3)
  - Research Policies, 4/69-11/1980; PR 2 (Box 6, Folder PR 2)
  - Accounting Revision Project, 6/1979-7/1981; A-21 (Box 6, Folder A-21)
  - DoD Sponsored Research, 10/80-4/1981; R3.3 (Box 6, Folder R3.3)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Ed., 1/78-8/1981; 3.1 (Box 7, Folder 3.1)
  - American Council on Education', 9/1979-4/1980; 3.8 (Box 7, Folder 3.8)
  - Nat'l. Assoc. of Independent Colleges and Univs., 1/1979-7/1981; 3.1 (Box 7, Folder 3.1)
  - Institute of International Education, 1/1979-7/1981; 3.38 (Box 7, Folder 3.38)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1981; 3.43 (Box 7, Folder 3.43)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1980; 3.43 (Box 7, Folder 3.43)
  - National Collegiate Athletics, 9/1979-8/1981; 3.44 (Box 7, Folder 3.44)
  - Assn. of Intercollegiate Athletics for Women, 10/80-6/1981; 3.45 (Box 7, Folder 3.45)
  - PAC 10, 8/1981--12/1981; 3.47 (Box 7, Folder 3.47)
  - Other Universities and Colleges, 1/80-7/1981; 0.8 (Box 7, Folder 0.8)
  - Assoc. of American Universities, 9/80-8/1981; 8.7 (Box 7, Folder 8.7)
  - Harvard University, 6/80-6/1981; 8.23 (Box 7, Folder 8.23)
  - University of California, 1/80-6/1981; 8.43 (Box 7, Folder 8.43)
  - Western Assoc. of Schools and Colleges, 10/80-6/1981; 8.52 (Box 7, Folder 8.52)
  - Committee on Earthquake Preparedness, 10/80-8/1981; C 6.7 (Box 8, Folder C 6.7)
  - Committee on Services to Students, 10/80-6/1981; C 6.9 (Box 8, Folder C 6.9)
  - Comm. on Investment Responsibilities, 11/80-8/1981; C 7.7 (Box 8, Folder C 7.7)
  - Commission on Investment Responsibilities, 1971; C 7.7 (Box 8, Folder C 7.7)
  - Commission on Investment Responsibilities, 29312; C 7.7 (Box 8, Folder C 7.7)
  - Investment Response-South Africa, 1976-77; C 7.7 (Box 8, Folder C 7.7)
  - Commission on Investment Responsibilities, C 7.7 (Box 8, Folder C 7.7)
  - Trustees: Special Committee on Investment, 1977-78; C 7.7 (Box 8, Folder C 7.7)
  - Responsibilities, C 7.7 (Box 8, Folder C 7.7)
  - Trustees: Special Committee on Investment Responsibilities, 1976-77; C 7.7 (Box 8, Folder C 7.7)
  - University Advisory Comm. on Budget Planning, 11/1979-8/1981; C 7.13 (Box 8, Folder C 7.13)
  - Committee on Parking and Transportation, 7/80-8/1981; C 8.1 (Box 8, Folder C 8.1)
  - Scientific Policy Committee, 1/1979-11/1981; C 8.4.1 (Box 8, Folder C 8.4.1)
  - PEP Policy Committee, 4/1979-1/1981; C 8.4.2 (Box 8, Folder C 8.4.2)
  - Administrative Panel on Health and Safety, 12/80-8/1981; C 8.10 (Box 8, Folder C 8.10)
  - Committee of Fifteen, 9/80-8/1981; C 9.2 (Box 8, Folder C 9.2)
  - Honor Code Commission, 7/1981-4/1981; C 9.5 (Box 8, Folder C 9.5)
  - University Policy, Misc. Matters, 11/76-7/1981; AD 2 (Box 8, Folder AD 2)
  - Facilities for the Handicapped, 2/80-7/1981; AD 2.11 (Box 8, Folder AD 2.11)
  - President, 29373; AD 4.1 (Box 8, Folder AD 4.1)
  - Presidential Chrons., 30286; AD 4.2 (Box 8, Folder AD 4.2)
  - Presidential. Chrons., 1.1/1982; AD 4.3 (Box 8, Folder AD 4.3)
  - President's Chrons., 30225; AD 4.3 (Box 9, Folder AD 4.3)
  - Chron. File, Pres. Kennedy, 30195; AD 4.1/1 (Box 9, Folder AD 4.1/1)
  - Chron. File, Pres. Kennedy, 30164; AD 4.1/1 (Box 9, Folder AD 4.1/1)
  - Chron. File, Pres. Kennedy, 30133; AD 4.1/1 (Box 9, Folder AD 4.1/1)
  - President's Chrons., 29677; AD 4.1/1 (Box 9, Folder AD 4.1/1)
  - President's Chrons., 29738; AD 4.1/1 (Box 9, Folder AD 4.1/1)
  - President's Chrons., 29587; AD 4.1/1 (Box 9, Folder AD 4.1/1)
  - President's Chrons., 29646; AD 4.1/1 (Box 9, Folder AD 4.1/1)
  - President's Chrons., 29768; AD 4.1/1 (Box 9, Folder AD 4.1/1)
  - President's Chrons., 29707; AD 4.1/1 (Box 9, Folder AD 4.1/1)
  - President's Chrons., 29618; AD 4.1/1 (Box 9, Folder AD 4.1/1)
  - President's Chrons., 29799; AD 4.1/1 (Box 9, Folder AD 4.1/1)
  - President's Chrons., 29556; AD 4.3 (Box 9, Folder AD 4.3)
  - President's Chrons., 29526; AD 4.3 (Box 9, Folder AD 4.3)
  - President's Chrons., 29495; AD 4.3 (Box 9, Folder AD 4.3)
  - President's Chrons., 9/80; AD 4.3 (Box 10, Folder AD 4.3)
  - President's Chrons., 29434; AD 4.3 (Box 10, Folder AD 4.3)
  - President's Schedule, 9/80-8/1981; AD 4.9 (Box 10, Folder AD 4.9)
  - Presidential Staff Meetings, 8/80-6/1981; AD 4.11 (Box 10, Folder AD 4.11)
  - Administrative Council, 5/80-8/1981; AD 4.12 (Box 10, Folder AD 4.12)
  - T-Z General, Misc., 7/80-4/1984; AD 4.20 (Box 10, Folder AD 4.20)
  - Schiffman, Max, 7/1983-4/1984; AD 4.20.5 (Box 10, Folder AD 4.20.5)
  - Students on committees: Policy, 1980-81; AD 8.5 (Box 10, Folder AD 8.5)
  - Career Planning and Placement Center, 29221; AD 8.7 (Box 10, Folder AD 8.7)
  - Stanford Program in Berlin, 4/80-8/1981; AD 8.11.4/2 (Box 10, Folder AD 8.11.4/2)
  - Financial Aids, 9/80-7/1981; AD 8.12 (Box 10, Folder AD 8.12)
  - Housing: Faculty, Staff, Emeriti, 1982; AD 8.18 (Box 10, Folder AD 8.18)
  - 1/1981-6/81, AD 8.18 Housing: Faculty, Staff, Emeriti (Box 10, Folder AD 8.18 Housing: Faculty, Staff, Emeriti)
  - Minorities, 4/80-7/1981; AD 9 (Box 10, Folder AD 9)
  - 1/80-8/81, AD 9.21 Stanford Ctr. for Chicano Research (Box 10, Folder AD 9.21 Stanford Ctr. for Chicano Research)
  - Staff Affirmative Action Program, 1981; AD 9.6 (Box 10, Folder AD 9.6)
  - Staff Affirmative Action Program, 1980; AD 9.6 (Box 10, Folder AD 9.6)
  - Personnel and Employee Relations, 10/80-7/1981; AD 10 (Box 10, Folder AD 10)
  - Management and Organization (Self-Study), 1980-81; AD 10.3 (Box 10, Folder AD 10.3)
  - United Stanford Employees, 11/80-5/1982; AD 10.7.8 (Box 11, Folder AD 10.7.8)
  - Grievance Hearings/Cases, 29221; AD 10.8.10/1 (Box 11, Folder AD 10.8.10/1)
  - Grievance File-Ming Pai, 11/1981-5/1982; AD 10.8.10/1 (Box 11, Folder AD 10.8.10/1)
  - Pekurovskaya Grievance, 8/77-5/1982; AD 10.8.10/1 (Box 11, Folder AD 10.8.10/1)
  - JoAnne Wetzel-Grievance File, 3/78-8/1981; AD 10.8.10/1 (Box 11, Folder AD 10.8.10/1)
  - Salaries, 6/1979-6/1981; AD 10.8.19 (Box 11, Folder AD 10.8.19)
  - Commencement 1981, AD 11.7.2 (Box 11, Folder AD 11.7.2)
  - Commencement Advisory Group, 1978-79; AD 11.7.2/1 (Box 11, Folder AD 11.7.2/1)
  - Business and Finance, 9/78-9/1981; AD 12.2 (Box 11, Folder AD 12.2)
  - Budget, 1/1981-4181; AD 12.5 (Box 11, Folder AD 12.5)
  - Health and Safety, 1/1981-7/1981; AD 12.8.1 (Box 11, Folder AD 12.8.1)
  - Office of Development, 5/80-8/1981; AD 12.10.1 (Box 11, Folder AD 12.10.1)
  - The Carnegie Foundation of New York, 10/1979-8/1981; AD 12.10.3/5-10 (Box 11, Folder AD 12.10.3/5-10)
  - 3/80-8/81, AD 12.10.3/5-43 Dr. and Mrs. J.E. Wallace Sterling (Box 12, Folder AD 12.10.3/5-43 Dr. and Mrs. J.E. Wallace Sterling)
  - International Business Machines, 10/80-12/1981; AD 12.10.3/5-51 (Box 12, Folder AD 12.10.3/5-51)
  - Prospective Donors, 4/80-6/1982; AD 12.10.3/12 (Box 12, Folder AD 12.10.3/12)
  - Foundations, Funds, Misc., 8/80-7/1982; AD 12.10.4 (Box 12, Folder AD 12.10.4)
  - Danforth Foundation, 9/1979-7/1980; AD 12.10.4/55 (Box 12, Folder AD 12.10.4/55)
  - Ford Foundation, 3/80-7/1981; AD 12.10.4/71 (Box 12, Folder AD 12.10.4/71)
  - Kresge Foundation, 9/1979-8/1981; AD 12.10.4/117 (Box 12, Folder AD 12.10.4/117)
  - The Henry Luce Foundation, 9/1979-6/1981; AD 12.10.4/126 (Box 12, Folder AD 12.10.4/126)
  - Andrew W. Mellon Foundation (Faculty Dev.), 4/80-8/1981; AD 12.10.4/139 (Box 12, Folder AD 12.10.4/139)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 10/1979-8/1981; AD 12.10.4/184 (Box 12, Folder AD 12.10.4/184)
  - Shell Companies Foundation, 9/1979-6/1981; AD 12.10.4/200 (Box 12, Folder AD 12.10.4/200)
  - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation, 2/80-7/1981; AD 12.10.4/204 (Box 12, Folder AD 12.10.4/204)
  - The Spencer Foundation, 9/1979-11/1981; AD 12.10.4/211 (Box 12, Folder AD 12.10.4/211)
  - National Multiple Sclerosis Society, 12/1979-6/1981; AD 12.10.4/287 (Box 12, Folder AD 12.10.4/287)
  - Athletic Department (Space), 9/1979-8/1981; AD 12.14.7/2 (Box 12, Folder AD 12.14.7/2)
  - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences, 1/80-12/1981; AD 12.14.7/16 (Box 12, Folder AD 12.14.7/16)
  - Tressider Memorial Union, 9/1979-8.81; AD 12.14.7/64 (Box 12, Folder AD 12.14.7/64)
  - Engineering, School of, Advisory Council, 10/80-5/1981; AD 13.10.5.7 (Box 12, Folder AD 13.10.5.7)
  - Emeriti Tea: Past Years, 12/1979-12/1980; AD 2.2.2 (Box 12, Folder AD 2.2.2)
  - Fellows of the University, 1/1979-10/1981; AD 2.9 (Box 12, Folder AD 2.9)
  - Stanford National Ratings/Accreditation, 7/80-6/1981; AD 3.4 (Box 12, Folder AD 3.4)
  - Rodin Collection/Cantor Gift, 6/1979-5/1982; AD 4.1.9/1 (Box 12, Folder AD 4.1.9/1)
  - Stanford Humanities Center, 1981-82; AD 4.1.12 (Box 12, Folder AD 4.1.12)
  - Economic Policy Research, Ctr. for, 10/1979-7/1980; AD 4.1.20/1 (Box 12, Folder AD 4.1.20/1)
  - Dept. of Athletics, Phys. Ed. and Rec., 8/80-9/1981; AD 4.1.30 (Box 12, Folder AD 4.1.30)
  - Music, 9/1979-5/1982; AD 4.1.29 (Box 12, Folder AD 4.1.29)
  - Graduate School of Business, 1/1979-6/1981; AD 4.2 (Box 12, Folder AD 4.2)
  - Center for Integrated Systems Development, 10/78-6/1981; AA 4.4.19 (Box 13, Folder AA 4.4.19)
  - School. of Education, 1/1979--8/1981; AA 4.5 (Box 13, Folder AA 4.5)
  - School of Medicine, 7/80-4/1981; AA 4.6 (Box 13, Folder AA 4.6)
  - Lucas, Zoltan J., M.D., 1/1979-6/1980; AA 4.6/3 (Box 13, Folder AA 4.6/3)
  - The Hoover Institution, 1981; AA 4.9 (Box 13, Folder AA 4.9)
  - 1981, AA 4.12.1 Research Libraries Group (RLG) (Box 13, Folder AA 4.12.1 Research Libraries Group (RLG))
  - 1979-80, AA 4.12.1 Research Libraries Group (RLG) (Box 13, Folder AA 4.12.1 Research Libraries Group (RLG))
  - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center, 1/80-8/1981; AA 4.13 (Box 13, Folder AA 4.13)
  - School of Law, 11/80-8/1981; AA 4.15 (Box 13, Folder AA 4.15)
  - Medical Center/Hospital, 9/80-8/1981; AA 4.17 (Box 13, Folder AA 4.17)
  - Stanford Hospital Bd. of Directors Meeting, 1981 Dec; AA 4.17.2 (Box 13, Folder AA 4.17.2)
  - SU Hospital Bd.' of Directors, 1981; AA 4.17.2 (Box 13, Folder AA 4.17.2)
  - Stanford Hospital Bd. of Directors, 1977-80; AA 4.17.2 (Box 13, Folder AA 4.17.2)
  - SU Hospital, Community Physicians Issue Bd. of Directors, 1981-82; AA 4.17.3 (Box 13, Folder AA 4.17.3)
  - Hospital Modernization Project, 1981; AA 4.17.5 (Box 13, Folder AA 4.17.5)
  - Stanford Center for Information Technology, 9/80-6/1981; AA 4.22 (Box 13, Folder AA 4.22)
  - Endowed Chairs/Professorships, Misc., 11/1979--8/1981; AA 10 (Box 13, Folder AA 10)
  - Visiting Professorship, Misc., 1/78-6/1981; AA 10.59 (Box 13, Folder AA 10.59)
  - Hoover Institution, Board of Overseers, 1/80-8/1981; AA 4.9.1 (Box 13, Folder AA 4.9.1)
  - Grievance File-Keith Goffney, 8/1981-5/1982; AD 10.8.10/1 (Box 13, Folder AD 10.8.10/1)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1985-004
  Conditions Governing Access note
  Restricted until 2019. Please consult the University Archivist for assistance.
  - AAU – Jt. Committee on Health Policy (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Academic Council (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Admissions (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Affirmative Action (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Alumni Association (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - ASSU (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Athletic Department (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Biotechnology Protest Pool (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Board of Trustees (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Board of Trustees – Secretary of Trustee Affairs (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Budget Cuts, Federal (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Budget Forecasts, Budget Staff (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Budget Group (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Cardiovascular Research (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Chemistry Prospects (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - C.I.S. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - C.I.T. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Committee for Corporate Support of Private Universities (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Conflict of Interest (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Consortium for Health Research Policy (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Crown Foundation (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Dean of Students Cases (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Development (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Disarmament, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - F Street Dinner, 1981 Mar 11 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - F Street Dinner, 1983 Mar 23 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Harvard University [out to legal office] (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Humanities and Sciences [out to legal office] (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Judicial System at Stanford University, 1980-82 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Management Development Program, 1981-83 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Mobius [publication], 1980-81 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Montgomery, Kenneth, 1981-82 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Institute of Medicine, 1979-82 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - NCAA, 1980-81 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Neurosciences Ph.D. Program, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Nitrites, 1980-81 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - NuWest Technology Conference, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - O'Connor, Sandra Day [Washington, DC reception], 1981 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Patent Extension Rule, 1981-82 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Professional Journalism Fellowship, 1980-82 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Stanford Engineering Executive Program, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - University Fellows, 1981-82 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Zabdyr, Zenona M., 1980 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1985-037
  - Stanford Historical Society, 9/77-6/1982; PAD 1.2 (Box 1, Folder PAD 1.2)
  - Std., Adm., Fac. Relations, 5/77-10/1981; PAD 1.4 (Box 1, Folder PAD 1.4)
  - Univ. Policy, Misc. Matters [permanently retrieved by the Legal Office], 9/1981-10/1981; PAD 2 (Box 1, Folder PAD 2)
  - Bicycles (Safety, Paths, etc), 2/1979-3/1982; PAD 2.1 (Box 1, Folder PAD 2.1)
  - Academic Freedom, 29037; PAD 2.6.1 (Box 1, Folder PAD 2.6.1)
  - Stanford Mascot/Symbol, 12/75-10/1981; PAD 2.7 (Box 1, Folder PAD 2.7)
  - Facilities for the Handicapped, 12/80-6/1982; PAD 2.11 (Box 1, Folder PAD 2.11)
  - Liquor Policy, 28764; PAD 2.15 (Box 1, Folder PAD 2.15)
  - Alcoholism, 3/1981-11/1981; PAD 2.15/1 (Box 1, Folder PAD 2.15/1)
  - ROTC, 9/78-7/1982; PAD 2.26 (Box 1, Folder PAD 2.26)
  - Campus Reports, 29403; PAD 3.4 (Box 1, Folder PAD 3.4)
  - Directories: Fac., Stf., Std., 29160; PAD 3.8 (Box 1, Folder PAD 3.8)
  - Fundamental Standard (Honor Code), 7/80-3/1982; PAD 3.10 (Box 1, Folder PAD 3.10)
  - Univ. Calendar/Holidays, 4/80-1/1982; PAD 3.21 (Box 1, Folder PAD 3.21)
  - Provost's Speeches [6/2010 not in box], 29342; PAD 3.22.1 (Box 1, Folder PAD 3.22.1)
  - President's Office, 1/80-11/1981; PAD 4 (Box 1, Folder PAD 4)
  - President, 29221; PAD 4.1 (Box 1, Folder PAD 4.1)
  - Presidential Power, 1/1979-11/1980; PAD 4.2 (Box 1, Folder PAD 4.2)
  - President's Schedule, 29037; PAD 4.9 (Box 1, Folder PAD 4.9)
  - Administrative Council, 9/1981-11/1981; PAD 4.12 (Box 1, Folder PAD 4.12)
  - Administrative Council, 29983; PAD 4.12 (Box 1, Folder PAD 4.12)
  - Administrative Council, 3/1982-5/1982; PAD 4.12 (Box 1, Folder PAD 4.12)
  - Academic Secretary, 1/1979-7/1982; PAD 4.14 (Box 1, Folder PAD 4.14)
  - University Counsel, 6/1979-6/1981; PAD 4.19 (Box 1, Folder PAD 4.19)
  - Nonsense/Complaints, 4/1979-12/1981; PAD 4.20.5 (Box 1, Folder PAD 4.20.5)
  - Recommendation Letters, 8/80-11/1981; PAD 4.20.6 (Box 1, Folder PAD 4.20.6)
  - Public Affairs Office, 6/1981-4/1982; PAD 4.22 (Box 1, Folder PAD 4.22)
  - Ombudsman, 12/80-6/1982; PAD 6 (Box 1, Folder PAD 6)
  - Legal Problems and Services, 6/1979-4/1980; PAD 7 (Box 1, Folder PAD 7)
  - Judicial Procedures/Charter, 28976; PAD 7.9 (Box 1, Folder PAD 7.9)
  - Admissions Office, 11/80-6/1982; PAD 8.1 (Box 1, Folder PAD 8.1)
  - Policy: Admissions, General, 8/78-3/1982; PAD 8.1.1 (Box 1, Folder PAD 8.1.1)
  - College Work Study Program, 29768; PAD 8.7.2 (Box 1, Folder PAD 8.7.2)
  - Dean of Student Affairs, 12/80-4/1982; PAD 8.8 (Box 1, Folder PAD 8.8)
  - Student Services and Spec. Serv. Office, 10/80-5/1981; PAD 8.8.2 (Box 1, Folder PAD 8.8.2)
  - Policy on Discrimination, 9/78-7/1979; PAD 8.8.3 (Box 1, Folder PAD 8.8.3)
  - Exchange Programs, 10/80-5/1982; PAD 8.10 (Box 1, Folder PAD 8.10)
  - Stanford Overseas Studies, 9/1981-6/1982; PAD 8.11 (Box 1, Folder PAD 8.11)
  - Stanford Overseas Studies, 30286; PAD 8.11 (Box 1, Folder PAD 8.11)
  - Stanford Center in Vienna, 29891; PAD 8.11.1 (Box 1, Folder PAD 8.11.1)
  - Stanford Center in Britain, 8/1981-1/1982; PAD 8.11.2 (Box 1, Folder PAD 8.11.2)
  - Stanford Center in Berlin, 5/1981-3/1982; PAD 8.11.4/1 (Box 1, Folder PAD 8.11.4/1)
  - Student Loans, 3/1981-2/1982; PAD 8.12.1 (Box 1, Folder PAD 8.12.1)
  - Financial Aids, 9/80-4/1982; PAD 8.12 (Box 1, Folder PAD 8.12)
  - Grad. Stud. Financial Aid, 3/1981-5/1981; PAD 8.12.2 (Box 1, Folder PAD 8.12.2)
  - Housing: Fac., Stf., Emrt., 7/1981-4/1982; PAD 8.18 (Box 1, Folder PAD 8.18)
  - Housing: Fac., Stf., Emrt., 9/1981-12/1981; PAD 8.18 (Box 1, Folder PAD 8.18)
  - Housing: Fac., Stf., Emrt., 4/80-7/1981; PAD 8.18 (Box 1, Folder PAD 8.18)
  - Housing: Fac., Stf., Emrt., 9/1981-6/1982; PAD 8.18 (Box 1, Folder PAD 8.18)
  - COIN Exceptions, 3/80-9/1982; PAD 8.18 (Box 1, Folder PAD 8.18)
  - Gardiner House, 8/1981-3/1982; PAD 8.18 (Box 1, Folder PAD 8.18)
  - Stanford West, 10/1981-5/1982; PAD 8.18 (Box 1, Folder PAD 8.18)